Guide to the Frank Baker collection of Methodist circuit plans, 1777-1984 and undated RL.00892
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- 19th Century Series, 1777-1961
  - Oldham Second (P):
    - 1875 Oct.-1876 Jan., Item #433 (Box 3)
  - Pately Bridge (P), 1841 Jan.-Apr., Item #283 (Box 3, Folder P-R)
  - Patrington (P), 1870 Jan.-Apr., Item #443 (Box 3)
  - Penrith, 1836 May-Oct., Item #37 (Box 3)
  - Penzance, 1835 Jan.-Apr., Item #130 (Box 3)
  - Penzance, 1837 Jan.-Apr., Item #154 (Box 3)
  - Plymouth, King St., 1872 Apr.-June, Item #264 (Box 3)
  - Pocklington (P), 1841 Jan.-Apr., Item #239 (Box 3)
  - Pocklington, 1961 Apr.-July, Item #33 (Box 3)
  - Pontefract (P), 1832 Sept.-Dec., Item #81 (Box 3)
  - Pontefract (P), 1841 Jan.-Apr., Item #325 (Box 3)
  - Preston:
    - 1822 Nov.-1823 Feb., Item #61 (Box 3)
    - 1827 Nov.-1828 Jan., Item #112 (Box 3)
    - 1828 Aug.-Oct., Item #67 (Box 3)
    - 1831 Aug.-Oct., Item #95 (Box 3)
    - 1834 May-July, Item #98 (Box 3)
    - 1843 Apr.-July, Item #331 (Box 3)
  - Preston and Chorley, 1857 Feb.-Apr., Item #345 (Box 3)
  - Preston, Lune St., 1877 Apr.-July, Item #415 (Box 3)
  - Preston (P), 1845 Feb.-Apr., Item #224 (Box 3)
  - Reeth, 1869 Feb.-Apr., Item #222 (Box 3)
  - St. Austell, 1959 Aug.-Oct., Item #34 (Box 3, Folder S1)
  - St. Helen's (P), 1875 Oct.-Dec., Item #417 (Box 3)
  - Salford-Manchester:
    - 1818 Aug.-Oct., Item #28 (Box 3)
    - 1826 Sept.-Nov., Item #122 (Box 3)
    - 1826 Dec.-1827 Feb., Item #123 (Box 3)
  - Scarborough (P), 1841 Jan.-Apr., Item #218 (Box 3)
  - Settle:
    - 1915 Nov.-1916 Jan., Item #333 (Box 3)
    - 1923 Jan.-Apr., Item #285 (Box 3)
    - 1925 Apr.-July, Item #132 (Box 3)
  - Shebbear (Bible Christian), 1873 Aug.-Oct., Item #236 (Box 3)
  - Sheerness, 1866 June-Sept., Item #190 (Box 3)
  - Sheffield, Carver St.:
    - 1883 July-Sept., Item #250 (Box 3)
    - 1891 July-Sept., Item #235 (Box 3)
    - 1891 Oct.-Dec., Item #249 (Box 3)
    - 1892 July-Sept., Item #231 (Box 3)
  - Sheffield (P), 1819 Dec.-1820 Feb., Item #1 (Box 3)
  - Sheffield (P), 1840 Nov.-1841 Jan., Item #286 (Box 3)
  - Shotley Bridge, 1879 May-July, Item #484 (Box 3)
  - Shrewsbury, 1826 Oct.-1827 Apr., Item #52 (Box 3)
  - Shrewsbury, 1830 May-Oct., Item #126 (Box 3)
  - Silsden: (Folder S2)
    - [1841] Jan-Apr., Item #280 (Box 3)
    - 1849 Apr.-July, Item #277 (Box 3)
    - 1849 July-Oct., Item #327 (Box 3)
  - Skipton, 1930 Jan.-Mar., Item #344 (Box 3)
  - Snaith:
    - 1825 Oct.-1826 Apr., Item #23 (Box 3)
    - 1818 Nov.-1819 Apr., Item #27 (Box 3)
    - 1864 Nov.-1865 Jan., Item #180 (Box 3)
  - Snaith (Prayer Leaders), 1864 Nov.-1865 Jan., Item #22 (Box 3)
  - Snaith, 1867 Nov.-1868 Feb., Item #221 (Box 3)
  - Spalding, 1895 May-July, Item #254 (Box 3)
  - Spalding, 1901 Jan.-Mar., Item #134 (Box 3)
  - Spilsby:
    - 1830 May-Nov., Item #217 (Box 3)
    - 1865 Nov.-1866 Feb., Item #436 (Box 3)
    - 1881 Mar.-June, Item #107 (Box 3)
    - 1881 Nov.-1882 Feb., Item #106 (Box 3)
    - 1895 Mar.-June, Item #178 (Box 3)
    - 1898 Oct.-1899 Feb., Item #177 (Box 3)
  - Stamford, 1837 July-Oct., Item #244 (Box 3)
  - Stamford, 189? May-July, Item #334 (Box 3)
  - Stirling and Down, 1859 Aug.-Dec., Item #7 (Box 3, Folder Sti-T)
    Handwritten plan. Removed from Jabez Palmer scrapbook--see Frank Baker Collection of Wesleyana and British Methodism, Volumes Series, Albums and Scrapbooks.
  - Stockport, [1835] July-Oct., Item #140 (Box 3)
  - Stockton, 1803 Nov.-1804 Apr., Item #65 (Box 3)
  - Stockton (P), 1838 Oct.-1839 Jan., Item #295 (Box 3)
  - Stokesley, 1839 Nov.-1840 Apr., Item #400 (Box 3)
  - Stourbridge, 1828 Aug.-Dec., Item #2 (Box 3)
  - Stratton and Bude (United Methodist), 1912 Oct.-Dec., Item #449 (Box 3)
  - Swinefleet (P):
    - 1832 Jan.-Mar., Item #55 (Box 3)
    - 1832 Apr.-June, Item #49 (Box 3)
    - 1832 July-Sept., Item #64 (Box 3)
    - 1832 Sept.-Dec., Item #60 (Box 3)
  - Tadcaster (P):
    - 1830 Oct.-1831 Jan., Item #214 (Box 3)
    - 1831 Apr.-July, Item #160 (Box 3)
    - 1831 July-Oct., Item #48 (Box 3)
  - Tadcaster, 1841 Jan.-Apr., Item #328 (Box 3)
  - Tunstall (P):
    - 1812 Mar.-June, Item #29 (Box 3)
    - (Variant)1812 Mar.-June, Item #125 (Box 3)
    - 1813 Nov.-Jan., Item #36 (Box 3)
  - Ulverston, 1877 Jan.-Apr., Item #306 (Box 3, Folder U-Wha)
  - Uttoxeter, 1874 May-July, Item #482 (Box 3)
  - Wainfleet:
    - 1882 July-Oct., Item #260 (Box 3)
    - [1888] Feb.-Apr., Item #342 (Box 3)
    - 1896 Apr.-July, Item #444 (Box 3)
  - Wakefield (P), 1837 Jan.-Apr., Item #233 (Box 3)
  - Wakefield, 1881 Oct.-1882 Jan., Item #367 (Box 3)
  - Wellington, 1818 May-Oct., Item #69 (Box 3)
  - Whalley (Chapel-Cleaning Plan), 1876-1877, Item #38 (Box 3)
  - Whitby, 1850 Nov.-1851 Apr., Item #351 (Box 3, Folder Whi-Y)
  - Whitby (P):
    - 1841 Jan.-Apr., Item #256 (Box 3)
    - 1843 Apr.-July, Item #161 (Box 3)
    - 1843 July-Oct., Item #155 (Box 3)
    - 1843 Oct.-1844 Jan., Item #153 (Box 3)
    - 1844 Apr.-July, Item #205 (Box 3)
  - Winster (P), 1843 Apr.-July, Item #266 (Box 3)
  - Wolsingham, 1875 Nov.-1876 Jan., Item #271 (Box 3)
  - Wolverhampton, 1883 Oct.-1884 Jan., Item #51 (Box 3)
  - Wrexham:
    - 1866 Sept.-Nov., Item #491 (Box 3)
    - 1866 Dec.-1867 Feb., Item #170 (Box 3)
    - 1867 Sept.-Nov., Item #164 (Box 3)
  - Wrexham (United Methodist), 1939 May-July, Item #18 (Box 3)
  - Yarmouth, 1881 Nov.-1882 Jan., Item #274 (Box 3)
  - York, 1853 May-Oct., Item #166 (Box 3)
  - York (Prayer Leaders), 1865 Apr.-Oct., Item #199 (Box 3)
  - Alford, 1949 Oct.-1950 Jan., Item #525 (Box 4 [Ovsz], Folder 1)
  - Bolton North, 1865 May-Sept., Item #519 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - Doncaster, 1872 Oct.-1873 Jan., Item #515 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - Driffield (P), 1841 Jan.-Apr., Item #502 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - Grimsby, 1864 Jan.-Apr., Item #517 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - Haslingden, 1839 Nov.-1840 Apr., Item #510 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - Hull, North, 1938 Jan.-Mar., Item #524 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - Kirkby Stephen, 1901 Apr.-July, Item #518 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - Liverpool (Conference Plan), 1847 July-Aug., Item #511 (Box 4 [Ovsz], Folder 2)
  - London, East:
    - 1819 Nov.-1820 Apr., Item #508 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
    - 1819 June-1820 Jan., Item #507 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
    - 1823 Apr.-Sept., Item #501 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - London (P), Third, 1862 Apr.-July, Item #527 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - London (Conference Plan), 1850 July-Aug., Item #516 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - Manchester, South:
    - 1825 Jan.-Apr., Item #520 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - Manchester (Conference Plan)
    - 1833 July-Aug., Item #521 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
    - 1841 July-Aug., Item #512 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
    - 1849 July-Aug., Item #523 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - Manchester Districts (Prayer Meetings), 1798 Jan.-Apr., Item #524 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - Manchester Districts (Prayer Meetings), 1798 Sept.-1799 Jan., Item #522 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - Oldham Second (P): (Folder 3)
    - 1872 Jan.-Apr., Item #513 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
    - 1872 Oct.-1873 Jan, Item #514 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - Otley (P), 1841 Jan.-Apr., Item #288 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - Ripon (P), 1840 Oct.-1841 Jan., Item #500 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - Swinefleet (P):
    - 1841 Jan.-Apr., Item #267 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - Wakefield, 1841 Jan.-Apr., Item #419 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
  - York (P), 1841 Jan.-Apr., Item #259 (Box 4 [Ovsz])
- Overseas Circuits Series, 1851-1896, 1946-1984
  - Australia: (Box 3)
    - New South Wales
      - Canterbury, 1954 May-July, Item #35 (Box 3)
      - Gordon, 1954 Aug.-Oct., Item #19 (Box 3)
      - Port Macquarie, 1954 Sept.-Oct., Item #92 (Box 3)
      - Mosman, 1954 Aug.-Oct., Item #96 (Box 3)
      - Victoria and Tasmania Leongatha, 1946 Aug.-Oct., Item #272 (Box 3)
  - Barbados, First, 1857 Dec.-1858 May, Item #435 (Box 3)
  - Bangalore, India, 1882 Apr.-June, Item #198 (Box 3)
  - Malvern, New Zealand, 1984 Feb.-Apr., Item #202 (Box 3)
  - Oyubia, Nigeria, 1958 July-Sept., Item #175 (Box 3)
  - Freetown, Sierra Leone, 1851 Apr.-July, Item #354 (Box 3)
  - Freetown, Sierra Leone, 1868 Aug.-Oct., Item #228 (Box 3)
  - Cape Town English Circuit, South Africa, 1892 Jan.-Mar. (Box 3)
  - Johannesburg, South Africa, 1896 July-Sept., Item #265 (Box 3)
  - Jamaica District (4 circuits), 1958 July-Sept. and Oct.-Dec., Items #414 and #404 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- 20th Century Series, 1896-1959, bulk 1944-1959 and undated, 9 boxes
  Donated at a later date. Approximately 1500 circuit plans, mainly covering the years from 1944-1959, but with scattered plans from the 1890s and 1900s. Plans are grouped alphabetically by circuit name (or city, if circuit unclear), but are not in order within each letter.
  - Information folder, 1955-1959 (Box 5)
  - A-B, 9 folders (Box 5)
  - B-C, 8 folders (Box 6)
  - D-H, 9 folders (Box 7)
  - H-L, 9 folders (Box 8)
  - L-N, 9 folders (Box 9)
  - N-R, 10 folders (Box 10)
  - R-S, 8 folders (Box 11)
  - S-W, 9 folders (Box 12)
  - W-Z and miscellaneous, 6 folders (Box 13)